[Music]
[音乐]
hello can you guys hear me fine hey hi
你好，你们能听到我很好吗嗨
hi everybody
大家好
hello boss Ilana welcome to beautiful J
你好老板伊拉娜欢迎来到美丽的J
hipster with spring bolt and beauteous
Spring 螺栓和美丽的时髦
how many of you here already used Blue
你们这里有多少人已经使用过Blue
Jays few how many of you loved that okay
周杰伦很少有人喜欢这个
you have a few hands great how many of
你有几只手很棒
you know what J hipster okay how many of
你知道J赶时髦的人好吗
you loved that few hands great thank you
你爱过那几只手，非常感谢
so pick up a little bit about me just
所以就跟我说一点
before we start in the session
在会议开始之前
I'm sending Kumar you can reach me at
我要寄给Kumar，您可以通过以下方式与我联系
this with a handle I'm basically from
这基本上是我的手柄
southern part of India Tamil Nadu and
印度南部的泰米尔纳德邦和
I'm currently living in the Netherlands
我目前住在荷兰
I'm work at a company called several
我在一家叫几家的公司工作
labs where we released a periodic table
我们发布周期表的实验室
for DevOps I'm a full-stack developer
对于DevOps，我是全栈开发人员
there I work on the entire application
在那里我负责整个应用程序
stack there and I'm also a code 2ft
堆在那里，我也是2ft的代码
member at a hipster I'm a big fan of
我非常喜欢某个时髦的成员
open source and I love open source
开源，我喜欢开源
contributing to it and I'm passionate
做出贡献，我充满热情
about it so if you guys want to start
关于它，如果你们想开始
with open source start learning stuffs
与开源开始学习的东西
and open source just reach out to me I
开放源代码就可以联系我
would try to help you guys okay so what
会尽力帮助你们，所以呢
we want to see today of course we see
我们今天想见，我们当然见
something about spring boot everybody
关于 spring boot 大家
knows about spring wood right who here
知道 Spring 的木头吧
haven't used spring boot before one ok
一口气还没用过 spring boot
great
大
and we will see a small demo in spring
我们将在春季看到一个小型演示
good it's nothing it's a simple demo but
很好，没什么，只是一个简单的演示，但是
I'll try it right in Cortland their
我会在他们的Cortland尝试
lifetime or something like that and then
一生或类似的事情，然后
we will see what Bluejays is all about
我们将看到Bluejays的全部意义
and we will try to generate a view js
我们将尝试生成一个视图js
application and then connect this vue.js
应用程序，然后连接此vue.js
application with the springboard
跳板的应用
application and then try and see how it
应用程序，然后尝试看看它如何
works together and finally we will
一起工作，最后我们将
showcase
展示柜
I will showcase watching hipsters all
我将展示观看潮人
about and then @m overture hipster how
关于然后@m序曲时髦如何
you can generate a full stack
您可以生成完整的堆栈
application which a hipster but view J
赶时髦但查看J的应用程序
is in the front end so that's what we
在前端，所以这就是我们
are gonna do today
今天要去做
Springwood so what a spring boot come on
斯普林伍德，所以 spring boot 来了
everybody used it right
每个人都用对了
sorry okay that that makes its that
抱歉，这使它
makes sense right
说得对
yeah so Spring Buddha actually makes it
是的，所以 Spring 的佛陀真的做到了
very easy and simple everybody knows
每个人都非常容易和简单地知道
here Springwood so I'm not gonna go deep
在这里斯普林伍德，所以我不会深入
dive into it it's like it embeds all
潜入它就像嵌入所有
these over for you you can choose a
这些给你，你可以选择一个
server and that helps you to create
服务器，这可以帮助您创建
production-ready application as well as
生产就绪的应用程序以及
testing or booting up your application
测试或启动您的应用程序
much more faster and it does a lot of
快得多，它做很多事情
automatic configuration which sometimes
自动配置有时
help you but if you want to drill down
帮助您，但如果您想深入了解
and make sure that you have to have more
并确保您必须拥有更多
performance and take or more performance
表现并取得或更高的表现
of the spring bootie have to like remove
Spring 的赃物必须喜欢删除
those automatic configurations and make
那些自动配置并
sure that you have customized
确保您已自定义
configuration so that's what springboard
配置，这就是跳板
is all about it makes it really easy to
全部就是它使得它真的很容易
develop web-based application spring or
开发基于Web的应用程序Spring或
Java web applications so let's go and
Java Web应用程序，让我们开始吧，
try as basic spring good application so
尝试作为基本的春季良好应用程序
what I'm going to do is like I'm just
我要做的就像我只是
going to download the repository or Qi
将要下载存储库或Qi
download some basic thing from spat the
从吐口水下载一些基本的东西
spring that I owe and I'm just going to
我欠的 Spring ，我正要去
add in certain dependencies like the
添加某些依赖项，例如
data JPA data rest and h2 I'm using a
数据JPA数据休息和H2我正在使用
Kotlin because it makes it very easy for
Kotlin，因为它非常容易
us to write it in a live demo project
我们在一个现场演示项目中编写它
and I'm using a bridle type and I'm just
我正在使用bri式，而我只是
giving a name as blog app and just do
命名为博客应用，然后做
this thing so it open it creates an
这个东西，所以打开它会创建一个
application for me so I can go ahead and
为我申请，这样我就可以继续
open this application in my IntelliJ how
在我的IntelliJ中打开此应用程序
many of you use IntelliJ only if you're
你们中的许多人只有在您
still using eclipse Emacs nobody yeah oh
仍在使用eclipse Emacs没人耶
using Emacs no okay
使用Emacs不好
oh wow let's start that
哦，让我们开始吧
so just importer the application it's a
所以只是导入应用程序
normal spring boot application nothing
正常的Spring Boot应用程序没有
fancy in it
喜欢它
so is it visible at the back is it okay
所以在后面可以看到吗
or do you do I want do you need to in
还是你想要我需要
cocaine a bit more
可卡因多一点
hope you increase the font size here
希望你在这里增加字体大小
Oh
哦
is it fine now no token yes yes I agree
现在可以了吗？没有令牌，是的，我同意
agree
同意
come on
来吧
anybody knows the shortcut for this nope
任何人都知道这种方式的捷径
sorry
抱歉
okay okay is it okay no thank you
好吧好吧好吧不，谢谢
okay so yes fine so what I'm going to do
好吧，是的，很好，我该怎么办
is like create a simple entity a block
就像创建一个简单的实体一样
entity that's it so gladly I have some
实体很高兴我有一些
life quote life code template here so
生活报价生活代码模板在这里，所以
what I've done have just created a date
我所做的只是创建了一个日期
a class with Kotlin and I just import
我和Kotlin一起上课
all those things it's a plane entity
所有这些都是平面实体
with a block with all those variables or
与所有这些变量的块或
field names in it and then what I have
字段名称，然后我有
to do next is like since I've also
接下来要做的就像因为我也
incorporated data JPA I just have to go
合并数据JPA我只需要走
to a go and add a repository so it's
去添加一个存储库，以便
like a interface that interfaces to JP a
就像与JP a接口的接口
repository so let me call it as block
仓库，所以我称它为块
repository which takes and blog and a
需要一个博客和一个仓库
long that's it and I have to annotate
就是这样，我必须注释
this guy with the repository not this
这个有仓库的家伙不是这个
one
一
so that's it right so I have my entered
没错，所以我输入了
a JP a layer or entire database layer
JP层或整个数据库层
available I also incorporated hatch too
可用，我也将舱口盖合并
so everything is done for me I have an
所以一切都为我做，我有一个
entity so I can do safe find everything
实体，以便我可以安全地找到所有东西
fine by ID and all those things inside
通过ID和里面的所有东西都可以
so what I can do is like I have to
所以我能做的就像
inject some data so let me go ahead and
注入一些数据，让我继续
do some data here so for that I'm gonna
在这里做一些数据，以便我
use the component runner let's block
使用组件运行器让我们阻止
sorry command line runner that extends
抱歉，扩展的命令行运行程序
command line runner and then implement
命令行运行器，然后实施
its member which is nothing but to run
它的成员不过是要跑
so again but I have to pass in a
再说一次，但我必须通过
repository here so I'll just pass in a
存储库在这里，所以我只传递一个
repository
资料库
which is nothing but a blog repository
就是博客库而已
so that's it right so I have this thing
这样就对了我有这个东西
available now so what I have to do here
现在可用，所以我在这里要做
is just inject some data inside and then
只是在里面注入一些数据，然后
see whether the data is populated when
查看何时填充数据
it's booting up so what I can do just go
它正在启动，所以我可以做的就是
ahead and create a list of a blog but
并创建一个博客列表，但是
Heidi with some content or with some
海蒂有一些内容或一些
title and some content I can copy and do
标题和一些我可以复制和执行的内容
the same
相同
put something else here put UJS here
在这里放其他东西在这里放UJS
since we are talking about that
因为我们在谈论那个
so it's it's plain simple things so what
所以这是简单的事情
I do next is like I have to save this so
接下来，我就像必须保存此文件
let me do for each and then I call this
让我为每个做，然后我称之为
repository dot save was in the entity so
存储库点保存在实体中，因此
that's it right so I just take all those
没错，所以我就把所有这些
values take that list run through the
值使列表贯穿
list and save those values there and do
列出并保存这些值，然后执行
and just to check when it's booting up
只是检查它何时启动
whether everything is saved what I can
是否一切都保存了我所能
do is like I can do find all the dot for
就像我可以找到所有的点
each again and then print that thing so
每次再打印该东西，这样
I can't stop and read on it so it's it's
我不能停下来继续读下去，就是这样
very simple right so you have one single
非常简单的权利，所以你只有一个
page of application finish so you have
应用程序完成页面，因此您拥有
one single application with just three
一个应用程序只有三个
different or four lines more you were
与您不同或多四行
able to create an application that that
能够创建一个应用程序
was able to do safe that was able to
能够做到安全，能够
find everything that was able to delete
找到所有能够删除的内容
and all those things so you have some
还有所有这些东西，所以你有一些
back-end running already right so that's
后端运行已经正确，所以
very simple about that's good about
关于这很简单
springboard it makes it really easy and
跳板，它真的很容易
with Kotlin it's again really easy or
使用Kotlin，这真的很容易，或者
freely shortened syntax
自由缩短的语法
correct but what about view so people
正确，但人们如何看待
who have used view why do you like view
谁使用过视图为什么您喜欢视图
no reasons just like that or you hate
没理由那样或你讨厌
all other frameworks that's why you like
所有其他框架，这就是为什么您喜欢
you okay we have a reaction here okay
你好，我们在这里有反应
great so about view we was actually an
太好了，关于视图，我们实际上是
indie develop train work which means
独立开发火车工作，这意味着
like no big company is behind the
就像没有大公司在背后
generation of you or people who are
你们这一代人或
developing views based basically
基本上基于观点
individually developed so that's one
单独开发，所以这是一个
thing and second thing is I it has
一件事，第二件事是我拥有
really an awesome community people in
真的是一个很棒的社区人
view really tend to help a lot and it
观点确实很有帮助，它
makes it very simple for you to get
使您轻松获得
started and running and if you stock up
启动并运行，如果您有库存
anywhere the community is there to help
社区可以帮助的任何地方
you out and it's really simple and
你出去，这真的很简单，
really easy just like Springwood how
真的像Springwood一样简单
Springwood makes development of web
Springwood开发Web
development in java pretty easy the same
用Java开发非常容易
way view actually helps it makes it very
视图实际上帮助它使其变得非常
simple to generate components it makes
易于生成的组件
it very simple to understand the things
理解事物非常简单
and it also make has a very easy
这也使它非常容易
structure to follow and get through it
遵循并通过它的结构
and if you want to learn view today for
如果您想今天学习视图
the people who haven't used view the
没有用过的人会看到
only place that you have to go is like
你唯一要去的地方就像
their own website UJ star which has
他们自己的网站UJ星
superb documentation with which you can
精湛的文档，您可以使用
learn everything out of it so it has
从中学习一切
clear flow of how you have to learn that
明确说明您如何学习
entire framework and you will get a lot
整个框架，您会收获很多
of information from that in that single
从那单的信息
website itself so if you have if you
网站本身，如果有的话
don't know but you just get over to that
不知道，但你只是克服了
website and get to know about view again
网站并再次了解视图
so if you're like me the very first
所以如果你像我一样
thing I will go and check if I'm going
我会去检查我是否要去
to do a project as go to github and
做一个项目，如去github和
watch out for the stars like how many
提防星星像几颗
stars does this project has and who is
这个项目有星星，谁是
using that thing for me angular the one
用那东西对我来说
framework that everybody uses before
大家以前使用的框架
angularjs I was talking about not
我在说不是
angular 8 so it has like 48 a stars and
角8，所以它有48颗恒星，
react has 2.5 times more than what
反应是它的2.5倍
angular had it's like 129 K but Vijay is
有角的，例如129 K，但Vijay是
half the biggest one which is like 2.6
最大的一半是2.6
times which is like around 140 K so it's
时间大约是140 K，所以
like everybody is using it it's even
就像每个人都在使用它，甚至
surpassed react make take a note view is
超过反应使记笔记是
school the reason why view school is
学校之所以看学校是
like it's progressive so what do you
喜欢进步，那你怎么办
mean by progressive here any guesses
这里的进步意味着任何猜测
come on it's just English word right so
来吧，这只是英文单词，所以
progressive so this is your web
进步的，所以这是你的网站
application right the front end of your
应用程序就在您的前端
application it has nothing but HTML and
应用程序，除了HTML和
JavaScript in it and some CSS who loves
其中的JavaScript和一些喜欢的CSS
writing CSS here okay we have one okay
在这里写CSS好吧，我们有一个好吧
so what do you do is slack with view you
所以你的工作是懈怠的
can just change a certain part of your
可以改变你的某个部分
application and change that into your
应用程序并将其更改为您的
view component and use it along with any
查看组件并将其与任何其他组件一起使用
other application that you have any
您拥有的其他应用程序
other stuffs that you might have and
您可能拥有的其他东西
then you can progressively enhance the
那么您可以逐步增强
other parts of the application and you
应用程序的其他部分以及您
can do that again and finally you can
可以再做一次，最后你可以
completely convert your application into
完全将您的应用程序转换为
a view based application so that's what
基于视图的应用程序，这就是
the progressive here means like it helps
这里的进步意味着它会有所帮助
you to progressively enhance your
您逐步增强您的
application from one frame up to another
从一帧到另一帧的应用
without having much troubles in doing
不用做很多麻烦
that and whatever view generates is
那和任何视图生成的是
reusable web component you have a single
可重用的Web组件，您只有一个
file in which you define everything that
在其中定义所有内容的文件
turns out to be a web component and this
原来是一个Web组件，而这
is a web component that you can use
是您可以使用的网络组件
anywhere in your application it doesn't
应用程序中的任何地方
mean that you have to use view or you
意味着您必须使用视图或
have to use it only inside a view
只能在视图内使用
application you can use it at any HTML
您可以在任何HTML上使用它的应用程序
or any place where JavaScript is valid
或JavaScript有效的任何地方
and hTML is valid so that is another
hTML是有效的，所以这是另一个
cool thing about view again it's simple
再次查看很酷的事情很简单
and easy so the other most important
和容易，所以另一个最重要的
thing of view is like it makes you to
观点就像它使你
write lesser code that is one of the
编写较少的代码，这是
great thing if you're writing an hello
如果您正在打个招呼，那就太好了
world application in angular and react
世界在角反应中的应用
and view view has very less amount of
并且视图视图的数量很少
code then compared to any of its
然后将代码与其任何
competitor because it's it's so close to
竞争对手，因为它是如此接近
the native HTML and JavaScript so it
原生HTML和JavaScript，因此
makes it really easy for you to write
让你写起来真的很容易
view so this is one hello world example
视图，所以这是一个世界示例
what I have here is nothing but a single
我这里只有一个
the first line is like you just import
第一行就像你刚导入
the view J's module and then you specify
视图J的模块，然后您指定
an ID app which is holder this is just
一个持有人的ID应用程序，这只是
an HTML and inside a script you define
HTML和您定义的脚本中
an object called new view that's it this
一个叫做新视图的对象就是这样
is just an object so everything in the
只是一个对象，所以
world of you is object so you just have
你的世界是对象，所以你只有
an object in JavaScript and you define
JavaScript中的对象，然后定义
the element data and some other stuff
元素数据和其他一些东西
inside it that's it this is a view
在里面就是一个视图
component you can use that view
您可以使用该视图的组件
component anywhere in user system so we
组件在用户系统中的任何地方，所以我们
have seen view components so this is the
看过视图组件，所以这是
general structure of view component you
视图组件的一般结构
can specify a data
可以指定一个数据
inside view components so this data is
内部视图组件，因此该数据是
the one that you're gonna show in your
你要显示在你的那个
templates how many of you know about
您知道多少的模板
templates
范本
okay so templates are nothing but HTML
好吧，模板就是HTML
right so you have this HTML and then you
对的，所以你有这个HTML，然后你
have the data inside that HTML you have
在您拥有的HTML中拥有数据
to do some data inside you have to show
在内部做一些数据必须显示
some values to the customers or the
给客户一些价值或
users who are using your application
使用您的应用程序的用户
that is the data so inside a view
那是数据，所以在视图内
component you can just specify a data
组件，您只需指定数据即可
which is again an object a bit funk
这又是一个有点放荡的对象
which is again a function but it's
这又是一个功能，但它是
analogous to an object in JavaScript
类似于JavaScript中的对象
everything is an object right so it's
一切都是对的，所以它是
analogous to object so you can show this
类似于物体，所以你可以展示这个
thing in daily inside a view component
日常在视图组件内部的事物
that said so this this is the one that
就是这样，这就是那个
you will represent inside a view
您将在视图中表示
component and the data that you're
组件和您要的数据
representing here is reactive which
代表这里是反应性的
means when you change the data it
意味着当您更改数据时
automatically changes the view and it
自动更改视图及其
can have certain methods these are the
可以有某些方法，这些是
methods that you might use like on click
您可能会点击使用的方法
on hover or on focus you want to call
悬停或要呼叫时要聚焦
the different function you want to call
您要调用的不同函数
another function that goes and talks to
与之交谈的另一个功能
your database all those things you put
您的数据库中放置的所有内容
inside the methods so the naming itself
在方法内部，因此命名本身
is so clear and concise here right so
在这里是如此清晰简洁
you have data this is the data that your
你有数据，这就是你的数据
friend or template needs and you have
朋友或模板的需求，你有
methods these are nothing but the
方法这些不过是
methods that you're gonna use in your
您将在自己的方法中使用的方法
template that's it so that's how it's
模板就是这样
named it's clear and concise and the
命名为简洁明了，
other hand views reactive how many of
另一方面看反应性有多少
you use spring buuut reactive here if we
如果我们在这里使用Spring buuut反应性
love that stuff one surprising okay
爱那个东西一个令人惊讶的好
so view is also reactive which means
所以视图也是反应性的，这意味着
like the entire thing is reactive so you
就像整个事情都是反应性的，所以你
have this view component which is
有这个视图组件是
nothing but your hash tml consider this
只不过你的哈希tml考虑了这一点
combination of HTML and JavaScript and
HTML和JavaScript的结合以及
every view component that you're
您所使用的每个视图组件
starting will have a watcher in it this
开始时会有一个观察者
watcher is nothing but a person who's
观察者不过是一个
considered himself as a person who is
认为自己是一个
sitting there and looking for any
坐在那里，寻找任何
changes that is happening in the system
系统中发生的变化
or looking for any changes that the
或寻找任何
particular data has in it so this is a
其中包含特定数据，所以这是一个
guy who sits there and watches what's
坐在那里看着什么的家伙
happening there and then you have this
发生在那里，然后你有这个
data where you define all the data that
数据，您可以在其中定义所有
is required for your entire component to
您的整个组件都需要
showcase to you and finally you have
展示给你，最后你有
this render render is nothing but hash
这个渲染渲染不过是哈希
tml which actually shows whatever things
tml实际上显示任何东西
that you want to show it select the
您想要显示它选择
presentation format of it so that's
它的演示文稿格式，所以
basically it so a view component has a
基本上，因此视图组件具有
watcher
看守人
which sits and watches whatever
坐着看什么
happening inside the data and based on
发生在数据内部并基于
that it goes and updates a rendered
它去更新渲染
field that's it
就是这样
so if you put that into this picture
所以如果你把它放进这张照片
it's like you have a view component with
就像你有一个视图组件
the watcher and the data have advocated
观察者和数据提倡
and setters this basically triggers the
和二传手这基本上触发了
rendering part of it and then you have
渲染它的一部分，然后你有
the render which actually renders the
实际渲染的渲染
virtual Dom tree everybody knows about
每个人都知道的虚拟Dom树
virtual Dom tree right yes okay so so
虚拟Dom树对，是，这样
that's it so when you when you set any
就这样，当您设置任何
value period it up so that's one let
珍惜期，所以让
your first intention is like you are
你的初衷就像你是
setting a value of two the data once
一次设置两个数据的值
you've set a value to the data the data
您已经为数据设置了一个值
will go and notify the watcher the
会去通知观察者
watcher lives inside the view component
观察者生活在视图组件中
it goes and notifies the watcher okay
它会通知观察者好吗
look the data that you're looking into
查看您正在寻找的数据
has been changed and the watcher what it
已经改变，观察者是什么
does is like it either renders if it's
确实就像它渲染了
already rendered it will read under the
已经呈现的内容将在
center application again so it goes and
再次将应用程序居中
tells okay it's time for you to render
告诉你是时候渲染了
and the render function will look and
渲染函数的外观和
then render the virtual Dom tree again
然后再次渲染虚拟Dom树
and once of ritual drom tea is rendered
并提供一次仪式的茶
what it does is like it goes back and
它所做的就像回去
renders the Dom tree that you actually
呈现您实际的Dom树
have that is your host Enoch page and
拥有您的主机Enoch页面，并
any interactions that you do on the
您在
system or on the browser what it does is
系统或浏览器上的功能是
like you're going to get a value from
就像你将从中获得价值
the data and this data is collected as a
数据，这些数据作为
dependency and stored as a stored in the
依赖项并存储为
watcher that's basically what's
观察者基本上是什么
happening so watcher is responsible for
发生，所以观察者负责
looking out for any changes in the
寻找任何变化
system and if there is a change watcher
系统以及是否有变更观察者
goes and nudges the render to change the
去微调渲染以更改
Dom that's it that's what watch it does
Dom就是手表的功能
and then you have this data which has a
然后你有这个数据有一个
getter and setter when you set a new
设置新的getter和setter
value to the data it goes and tells the
数据的价值，并告诉
watcher go and change everything that
观察者去改变一切
you have in the render clear okay
您已经在渲染中清楚了吗
and in bluej is everything is object in
在bluej中，一切都是对象
JavaScript again everything is an object
JavaScript再次一切都是对象
so when you go back view days everything
因此，当您返回查看日期时，一切
is object to which means like whatever
是对象意味着什么
you're generating whatever you're making
你正在产生你正在做的一切
a component that you're defining is an
您定义的组件是
object that's it so let's go ahead and
对象就是这样，让我们​​继续前进，
create a view J's app and then try to
创建视图J的应用，然后尝试
connect with the backend that we already
与我们已经连接的后端连接
have it running and then see what
运行它，然后看看
happens now so let me go back to the
现在发生了，所以让我回到
terminal again so so vu j s has CLI
再次终端，所以vu js具有CLI
which is similar to create react app ng
类似于创建反应应用程序
CLI anybody used about ng CLI or
CLI任何使用过ng CLI的人或
create react tap yep so it's like just a
创建react tapyep就像一个
bootstrapping the entire application for
引导整个应用程序
you it sets up all the default values
您将设置所有默认值
that you might need to generate an
您可能需要生成一个
application so in view we have something
应用程序，所以鉴于我们有一些东西
called view CLI so it has an NPM module
称为视图CLI，因此它具有NPM模块
you can install with NPM install view
您可以使用NPM安装视图进行安装
CLI and once you've installed you have
CLI，安装完成后，
this view command available you can go
您可以使用此视图命令
ahead and type you create given I name
向前键入您创建的给定名称
okay so let me call it as blog view so
好吧，让我称之为博客视图
what it does is like it asks me a bunch
它的作用就像是问我一堆
of questions and based on the question
问题，并基于问题
is generates me the india application
是生成我印度应用程序
that I might need so I'll go ahead and
我可能需要，所以我继续
show the manual select features so here
显示手动选择功能，因此在这里
even choose a bable bable is a
甚至选择一个圣经圣经是一个
transpiler that helps you to transpile a
转译器，可帮助您转译
format of code into another format of
代码格式转换为另一种格式
code how many of you don't know about
编码你们中不知道多少人
babel here okay if you have you so
巴别在这里好吧，如果你有你的话
similar to you can consider this is
类似于你可以认为这是
similar to generated think that converts
类似于产生转换的想法
Scotland into Java and then run in a JVM
将苏格兰移植到Java中，然后在JVM中运行
it's similar to come to a Java Script
类似于Java脚本
into JavaScript and then run in
进入JavaScript然后运行
JavaScript machines that's what apple is
JavaScript机器就是苹果
all about and then you have typescript
所有关于，然后你有打字稿
if you want to use typescript you can go
如果您想使用打字稿，可以
ahead and use it and the routers and
提前使用它以及路由器和
view X is something like protects how
视图X就像是保护
many of you know about redux here
你们当中很多人都知道redux
there's a lot of new things here okay so
这里有很多新东西，所以
relax is a state management library that
Relax是一个状态管理库，
all friends and people are using so if
所有的朋友和人们都在使用，如果
you want you can add and view X also
您想也可以添加和查看X
there and then you have set of other
在那里，然后你有其他
things which is not needed or which is
不需要或不是的东西
needed based on your purpose let me go
根据您的目的需要让我走
ahead and choose the default stubs and
并选择默认存根，然后
use the lien thing and there are a lot
用留置权的东西，有很多
of configuration files that will be
的配置文件
generated so I want to dedicate leak on
产生，所以我想专门泄漏
generate them in a separate file so I
在一个单独的文件中生成它们，所以我
was just generated and then I'm just
是刚刚产生的，然后我只是
generated the app that's it so any
生成了就是这样的应用程序
application will be generated for me and
应用程序将为我生成
the next step is like I can go ahead run
下一步就像我可以继续运行
this application and see what it does so
这个应用程序，看看它是怎么做的
basically what happens now is like it
现在基本上发生了什么
generates an entire boilerplate that I
生成一个完整的样板
need once it's done it installs all the
完成后就需要安装所有
dependencies that I might need end up
我可能需要的依赖最终
for the application to run and once it
让应用程序运行并运行一次
is done then I can start the application
完成后，我可以启动应用程序
and see how the application is generated
并查看如何生成应用程序
so this is a block view that we have
所以这是我们的方块图
generated so as you can see here the no
生成，因此您可以在这里看到
modules are getting installed which
正在安装哪些模块
obviously downloads the Internet and
显然会下载互联网并
makes everybody's Internet's to slow and
使每个人的互联网变慢，
you have the center source repository in
您在其中有中心源存储库
which all the things resides this is
所有的东西都存在这是
your entry point of your application so
您的应用程序入口点
this entry point you're defining
您定义的这个入口点
importing view from the Central Library
从中央图书馆导入视图
and then you sing the view that's it and
然后你唱的就是它，
then you define a component called AB
然后定义一个称为AB的组件
dot view which is where you are gonna
点视图，这是您要去的地方
define everything that you want to do so
定义您想要这样做的一切
this AB dot view is a view component by
这个AB点视图是一个视图组件
itself as you can see you have a single
正如你所看到的，你只有一个
you are exporting that component that's
您正在导出该组件
it you're not doing anything else and
如果你什么都没做，
you have some Styles attached to it and
您已经附加了一些样式，并且
this is the template template are
这是模板模板
nothing but your HTML so inside the
只不过是您的HTML，所以在
house tml you are specifying an image
您正在指定图片的房子tml
and a hello world this hello world is
和一个你好世界，这个你好世界是
another component that you have it here
您在这里拥有的另一个组件
so this is another component here you
所以这是这里的另一个组成部分
have lists of things inside some page
在某些页面内有事物列表
and that's it so it also is exported as
就这样，它也被导出为
a component so you can go back and see
组件，以便您可以回去看看
here
这里
okay this is because it is not sitting
好吧，这是因为它没有坐着
okay let me go back
好吧，让我回去
don't install again okay so it's because
不要再安装好了，这是因为
okay it went out but the main reason
好的，它出来了，但是主要原因
what happened is like when when you're
发生的事情就像当你
generating a man with application it you
用应用程序生成一个人
require to set up the logging level of
需要设置日志记录级别
the back plugin that we are using it's
我们正在使用的后插件
not by default set I thought it will be
没有默认设置我以为会
set by default but it's not set by
默认设置，但不设置
default so that Sarah that you have seen
默认值，这样您看到的Sarah
I'm just regenerating the entire
我只是重新生成整个
application with the default values this
具有默认值的应用程序
time it should work hopefully
时间应该有望
No okay
不好啦
damage control
损害控制
okay was doing this just before the
好吧，就在
presentation and everything was working
演示文稿，一切正常
fine thanks
很好，谢谢
okay so what we have here so let me just
好吧，所以我们在这里，所以让我
commend this guy see if this
赞这个家伙看看
and then copy the sky over
然后复制天空
this
这个
now let me see what happened okay that's
现在让我看看发生了什么
fine
精细
let me delete this guy so my application
让我删除这个人，这样我的申请
who finally okay the application is
谁终于同意了
running now so this is my Vijay's
现在正在运行，所以这是我的Vijay
application it's running okay so what it
应用程序运行正常，那又如何
has is the same thing I just remove this
有一样的东西，我只是删除了这个
extra content that I have it here so
我在这里有多余的内容
which means like it just says one value
这意味着它只是说一个价值
here so I can go back here you just
在这里，所以我可以回到这里，你只是
remove all those extract contents that I
删除所有我提取的内容
had here it just had a logo under this
在这里，它下面只有一个徽标
thing so what I can do now this like
事情，所以我现在可以做这样的事情
again okay so basically what I'm trying
再次好吧，所以基本上我正在尝试
to do now is like let's down the blocks
现在要做的就像让我们放下障碍
that I have in my back and application
我的背部和应用程序
and so it here that's that's what I'm
所以这就是我的意思
trying to do so what I can do first is
尝试这样做，我首先要做的是
like again rename this component into
就像再次将此组件重命名为
something else so I can rename it to
其他的东西，所以我可以重命名为
block listing block list so once I
阻止列表阻止列表，所以一旦我
renamed it I have to rename it here also
重命名了我也要在这里重命名
so let me go ahead and rename it here so
所以让我继续在这里重命名
yes it's done my application is not
是的，我的申请不是
broken perfect
破碎的完美
so once I have done this I I can say a
所以一旦我完成这个，我可以说一个
title here instead of a message so I can
在这里标题而不是消息，这样我就可以
say title equals a block list or I can
说标题等于黑名单，或者我可以
also give a message message welcome to
也给我们留言
spring i/o okay it's the end of the
Spring 我/好吧，这是结束
conference but still spring on your to
会议，但仍然会吸引您
zero one night can give this thing so
零一晚可以给这个东西，所以
these are called as the properties or
这些称为属性或
props that you add inside your
你在里面添加的道具
application or and I to this component
申请或与我对此组件
so inside the component you have defined
所以在您定义的组件内部
one prop which is the message which we
一个道具是我们所传达的信息
have already seen and it's type so you
已经看过了，它的类型是
can also go ahead and specify a title
也可以继续并指定标题
and then say it's a string so that's it
然后说这是一个字符串，就这样
right so here I've done this and then I
对，所以我在这里做了，然后我
can go and say h2 to and then I can say
可以去说h2到然后我可以说
title
标题
so as you can see here the title gets
所以您可以在这里看到标题
updated so I have this h2 here these are
更新，所以我有这个H2这些是
like simple things that you can do and
喜欢你可以做的简单的事情，
then I have to show a list so what I
然后我必须显示一个清单，所以我
will do is like again I can show a list
将要做的就像我可以显示一个列表
lu well this is simple HTML so you can
很好，这是简单的HTML，因此您可以
say you well and then you can say li
说你好然后你可以说李
content 1 and then you can say content -
内容1，然后您可以说内容-
so you can see here that my content 102
所以你可以在这里看到我的内容102
are getting added in here so what I get
被添加到这里，所以我得到
why it's showing a single it's because
为什么显示单个是因为
of the simple CSS I can remove this guy
简单的CSS我可以删除这个家伙
and it should show in a drop-down way so
它应该以下拉方式显示
next what I can do is like instead of
接下来我能做的就是代替
using this content I can just use a data
使用此内容，我只能使用数据
data that we have seen so far so how to
到目前为止我们已经看到的数据以及如何
use the data it's as simple as this you
使用数据就这么简单
go and add a data property here data and
去在这里添加数据属性data和
then say it says function written the
然后说说功能写了
value of return okay so let's call it as
返回的值还可以，所以我们称其为
block since that's what we are going to
阻止，因为这就是我们要
do and give an array so let's let it be
做并给出一个数组，所以让我们做吧
content 1 and content 2 and here what I
内容1和内容2，这里是我
can do is like I can remove this guy and
可以做的就像我可以删除这个人，
then I say put a for loop here so V 4
那我说在这里放一个for循环，所以V 4
which is a for loop that I have and then
这是我的for循环，然后
I can say item come on index n the
我可以说项目出现在索引n
blocks that I have and I have to specify
我必须指定的块
a key so to specify a key this is very
一个钥匙，所以要指定一个钥匙，这是非常
similar to react so key basically here
类似于反应，所以基本上在这里关键
uses to identify each of that element
用于识别每个元素
individually it's like an identifier
每个人就像一个标识符
that you have to put inside your
你必须放入你的
database your unique key or the primary
数据库您的唯一密钥或主键
key identifier something similar to that
密钥标识符类似于
it's very similar to that so I put index
这非常相似，所以我把索引
here which is a unique value because its
这是一个独特的价值，因为
site rating to that array of blocks and
对该区块块的网站评分和
then have an index which is like 0 1 2
然后有一个像0 1 2的索引
that will be added as a key it should be
将被添加为密钥
unique and I have this item all I have
独一无二，我拥有这个物品
to do is like add this item inside here
要做的就像在这里添加此项目
so this should have the same thing so
所以应该有同样的东西
you can see it my application generator
你可以看到它我的应用程序生成器
so I'm using a data now but what I
所以我现在正在使用数据，但是我
basically want to use is like I have to
基本上想使用就像我必须
hit my back end of
打我的后端
application and then get the data from
应用程序，然后从中获取数据
there so for that I need to have a
为此，我需要一个
method so what I can do is I can go
方法，所以我能做的就是我可以去
ahead and say methods which is an object
向前说是对象的方法
so here I can define list of functions
所以在这里我可以定义功能列表
which I can call from my interface or
我可以从我的界面或
from my view component so I'm going to
从我的视图组件，所以我要
get blocks as a function so it's a
获取功能块，所以它是一个
function so what it does is like it
功能，所以它的作用就是这样
returns this component or just array for
返回此组件或只是数组
now and all I have to do is like this
现在，我要做的就是这样
don't get blocks that's it so now I have
不要得到块，就这样我有了
something so it should be working so yes
东西，所以它应该工作，所以是的
it's working so what i'm doing here is
它正在工作，所以我在这里做的是
nothing but instead of directly giving a
什么都没有，而是直接给
value i'm calling a method or a function
值，我正在调用方法或函数
and from that function and just going
然后从那个功能开始
and returning a value here but here i
并在这里返回值，但在这里我
can also do this thing I can say this
我也可以这样说
dot blocks so this is this view
点块，所以这是这个视图
component this dot blocks blocks is the
该点阻止的组件是
data that is available here which is
此处可用的数据是
equal to this content so this will also
等于此内容，所以这也将
this will not show you anything
这不会显示任何内容
hopefully this should have shown
希望这应该已经表明
something what I'm doing wrong yes okay
我做错了什么事，是的
okay it should be returned sorry I'm two
好吧，应该归还，我两岁
steps ahead No okay so it should return
向前走不好，所以应该返回
a value so it should have something here
一个值，所以它应该在这里
so yes so what I have to do I have to
所以是的，所以我必须要做的是
connect with the third server or the
与第三台服务器或
server that I have to connect is running
我必须连接的服务器正在运行
on localhost 8080 so I can use the
在本地主机8080上，因此我可以使用
simple fetch here fetch okay fetch
简单获取这里获取好获取
and then I get a response okay so here
然后我得到回应，所以在这里
and the fare for the fetching I should
还有我应该提取的票价
go to the blocks endpoint which is where
转到块终点
my NDA application will return a blocks
我的NDA应用程序将返回一个块
and then if I have to just do responds
然后如果我必须做回应
so Jason and I have something here which
所以杰森和我在这里有一些东西
is blogs so just before that we can see
是博客，所以在此之前，我们可以看到
how the content is so spring mid-spring
Spring 的内容如何如此
data resource you have content something
您拥有的数据资源内容
like this so it gives you a content like
这样，它给你的内容像
this but it's inside actually inside the
这个，但实际上在里面
embedder which is inside the blocks and
块内的嵌入器和
it has a list of things that you have it
它列出了您拥有的东西
here so all I have to do is like the
在这里，我要做的就是
same thing this dude looks is equal to
这个家伙看起来和那一样
the contents of this thing okay so it's
这个东西的内容还可以，所以
like blocks dot embedded dot blocks
像块点嵌入式点块
so it won't show me anything because of
所以它不会显示任何东西，因为
the CRS you have to enable CRS which we
CRS，您必须启用我们的CRS
haven't done it so I will go back to my
还没有完成，所以我会回到我的
app and what I can do is like I can
应用程序，我能做的就是
enable rest repository here so
在此处启用rest仓库
repository rest resource and I can
存储库剩余资源，我可以
specify cross origin with some values or
用一些值指定交叉原点或
sorry origins
对不起的来历
so my application is running on 8081 so
所以我的应用程序在8081上运行
I just have to specify that restart my
我只需要指定重启我的
application
应用
so you can see here something is there
所以你可以看到这里有东西
so it comes out here so what I have to
所以它出现在这里，所以我必须
do now is like just to change my
现在要做的只是改变我的
application so here I'm just printing
应用程序，所以这里我只是打印
this item so it's not ideal
这个项目，所以不理想
it should not be item it should be item
它不应该是项目它应该是项目
door title and hopefully this should be
门的标题，希望这应该是
hash three and then let's put a color to
哈希三，然后让颜色
it
它
so you can see here it's there and I
所以你可以看到这里和我
have something called content so let me
有一些叫做内容的东西，所以让我
add the content to
将内容添加到
and line two separate them
第二行将它们分开
can we add some width to the line so
我们可以给线增加一些宽度吗
just like that does that subtract you
就像那样会减去你
have this entia listing page
拥有这个entia列表页面
for the block but nothing down and the
对于块，但没有下降，
amount of code that you have written is
您编写的代码数量是
just this one component now we can go
只是这一部分，我们现在可以
ahead and use this view component or
并使用此视图组件或
book it's named as hello world but you
预订它的名字叫你好世界，但是你
can change it to block listing and
可以更改它以阻止列表和
things like that but you can have the
这样的事情，但你可以拥有
single component and then use it
单个组件然后使用它
anywhere in your application you can use
您可以在应用程序中的任何位置使用
it multiple times you can use it at any
它可以多次使用
point of time so that's how beauteous
时间点，所以这是多么美丽
imple and it's like what I have done is
简单，就像我所做的是
like you have defined a data and also
就像您定义了数据一样
you have to find a list of methods
您必须找到方法列表
inside the data that's it so you haven't
里面的数据，所以你没有
done here the reason why I haven't
在这里做了我为什么没有的原因
returned anything and using this thing
返回任何东西并使用这个东西
is like this nth chunk of code will run
就像这第n个代码块将运行
asynchronously it's not synchronous
异步，它不是同步的
running it's a synchronous running so
运行它是同步运行的，所以
your event loop goes away from it it
您的事件循环会远离它
doesn't return anything so it will be
不返回任何东西，它将是
set as empty and once the switch is
设置为空，一旦开关为
completed once you get the data back
取回数据后完成
then it sets a value of inside this dot
然后在这个点内设置一个值
blocks which updates of you rearend s
阻止您更新哪些更新
entry so that's it so that's how it
条目，就这样，就这样
works so that's how you make sit really
有效，这就是您真正坐下来的方式
simple for you to ride the front end and
对您而言，骑乘前端很简单，并且
also with springboard you can ride a
还有跳板，你可以骑
minimal number of code and then write
最少数量的代码，然后编写
everything out of the box runs out of
开箱即用的一切
the box so J hipster so then this is the
盒子，所以J时髦所以这是
last part of the presentation J hipster
演讲的最后部分J时髦
so what is J hipster anybody who have
那么J时髦的人
used it yes what has Dave do
是的，戴夫做了什么
yes correct so the generator that helps
是的，所以发电机对您有帮助
you to generate a full stack application
您生成一个完整的堆栈应用程序
but we've it's basically it's nothing
但我们基本上没有
but Java hipster and what it does is we
但是Java潮人，它的作用是我们
like to call them as a development
喜欢称他们为发展
platform because it tries to generate
平台，因为它尝试生成
the application the entire application
应用程序整个应用程序
and also they helps you to develop and
而且它们还可以帮助您发展和
deploy applications you get the CI CD
部署获得CI CD的应用程序
off of the box you get of cubanelles
开箱即用的古巴
configuration or micro services
配置或微服务
application everything right over the
应用一切
box it it lists down everything that you
框上它列出了您的所有内容
need as a developer to start working on
需要作为开发人员来开始工作
day one from day one and just focus on
从第一天开始的第一天
your functionality you can go ahead and
您的功能可以继续
customize it because whatever we are
自定义它，因为无论我们是谁
trying to be a generating are nothing
试图成为一代人不是什么
but simple spring boot plus single page
但是简单的Spring Boot加单页
applications so YJ hipster y yes yes
应用程序，所以YJ时髦y是是
it's fast to start yes any other nope
快速开始是的，其他任何方式
it's faster development it helps you to
开发速度更快，可帮助您
start really fast go faster and as
快速开始，走得更快，
developer it increases your experience
开发人员可以增加您的体验
because there might be people who will
因为可能有人会
not know about the backend side of the
不知道后端
application they can go ahead and read
他们可以继续阅读的应用程序
the application understand half the
应用程序了解一半
back-end is wired for the people who
后端是为那些
don't know the front end they can go and
不知道他们可以去的前端
find out how the friend is wired the
找出朋友的接线方式
main problem with the software
该软件的主要问题
development at least novels like wiring
至少发展像接线这样的小说
things takes a longer time than doing
事情比做需要更长的时间
stuffs so with Jacob ster it's pretty
东西，所以用雅各布斯特
easy for you to develop faster and it
容易让您更快地发展
increases your experience that's one
增加您的经验之一
thing and we also make sure that we
事情，我们还要确保我们
always have latest libraries and
总是有最新的库和
frameworks incorporated which means that
纳入框架，这意味着
currently we have Java 12 based docker
目前我们有基于Java 12的docker
images and everything and we also use
图片和所有内容，我们也使用
Dib for integrating docker files which
Dib用于集成docker文件
is much faster than compared to normal
比正常速度快得多
dockable so it's like we always tried to
可停靠的，就像我们一直试图
find out the latest libraries and
找出最新的图书馆和
frameworks and make sure that we are hi
框架，并确保我们嗨
incorporating that in the application
将其合并到应用程序中
that makes you to develop applications
使您能够开发应用程序
much more faster and you have the latest
更快，您拥有最新的
features also enabled and finally it
功能也启用了，最后
also adds in and learning for you so it
还可以为您学习
increases our learning as a developer so
增加了我们作为开发人员的学习，因此
you can get to know different stuffs and
您可以了解不同的东西，
for me personally it helped a lot to
对我个人而言，这对
understand how the cuiprit is
知道cuiprit是什么
configuration and things like that or
配置和类似的东西或
how to deploy and run micro services and
如何部署和运行微服务，以及
things like that
像这样的东西
so that's also one other thing so let's
所以这也是另一件事，所以让我们
go and see
去看看
how we can generate blueprint of gesture
我们如何生成手势蓝图
with PJs so let me go back close the sky
与PJ合作，让我回去关闭天空
close this guy close this
关闭这个家伙关闭这个
go back here
回到这里
okay
好的
so all I have to do to do to Dungey
所以我要做的所有与Dungey相关的事情
hipster is like 2j hipster and then hit
赶时髦的人就像2j赶时髦的人，然后打
enter it asked me a set of questions I
输入它问了我一系列问题
just answered those questions and it
刚刚回答了这些问题，
asking me to generate an application but
要求我生成一个应用程序，但是
since we are talking about blueprint
因为我们在谈论蓝图
which is not available as a part of the
不能作为一部分
core generator it is something extended
核心生成器这是扩展的东西
out of the core generator so what I have
在核心生成器之外，所以我拥有
to do is like you have to specify this
要做的就像您必须指定此
thing - - blueprint UJS and what it does
东西-蓝图UJS及其作用
is like it goes ahead and 6:00
就像继续进行到6:00
oops ok great demo that I have hopefully
糟糕，我希望有一个很棒的演示
I have a backup for this
我对此有一个备份
get me have a backup I don't know what
让我备份我不知道
happened okay
好吧
okay let's try into deeper thing here
好吧，让我们在这里尝试更深的东西
such a hipster works
这样的时髦作品
okay so I think the dependency library
好的，所以我认为依赖库
is missing here that's why it's throwing
在这里丢失了，这就是为什么它抛出
me an error so let me try to install so
给我一个错误，让我尝试安装，这样
this is an additional library that you
这是您的附加库
have Jake hipster - boo Jas which is an
有杰克时髦-嘘贾斯这是一个
additional library that you have to
您必须附加的库
install it in your system and with that
将其安装在您的系统中
you can also you can generator of UJS
你也可以生成UJS
based application
基于应用
can have some project here so let me try
可以在这里有一些项目，所以让我尝试
one more time
再一次
no fantastic okay
没什么好吧
okay let me just go for the backup
好吧，让我去备份
project and see where I have the backup
项目，看看我有备份
project
项目
all my trials went really good but not
我所有的考验都很好，但不是
the application original demo yeah okay
应用程序原始演示是的，好的
we have it here
我们在这里
yes okay so I have it here this is the
是的，好的，我在这里，这是
basic application that is generated
生成的基本应用程序
which a hipster so what it basically
哪个时髦，所以基本上
does is like
确实就像
so when you run gesture it basically
因此，当您运行手势时，基本上
asks you set of questions and based on
问你一组问题，并根据
the questions it tries to generate an
它试图产生一个问题
application for you so I have that
申请给你，所以我有
option to choose between monolith and
整体式和
micro service so I just use the monolith
微服务，所以我只用整体
here the base name of your application
这是您的应用程序的基本名称
the package name for the java
Java的程序包名称
application and the registry if you want
应用程序和注册表（如果需要）
to use and then it asked you whether
使用，然后问你是否
which kind of authentication that you
您使用哪种身份验证
want to use either it be JWT or hash TTP
想要使用JWT或哈希TTP
or or what - session authentication so
或或什么-会话身份验证
you can choose this thing and it we will
您可以选择这个东西，我们会
configure the entire thing for you so it
为您配置整个事情
goes and builds just select the
去建立只是选择
tradability authentication the database
交易身份验证数据库
that we have to use the database for the
我们必须将数据库用于
production and also for the development
生产和发展
you can choose different databases will
您可以选择其他数据库
try to configure that inside there and
尝试在那里配置
also we have the spring cashy
我们也有 Spring 的现金
abstraction which you can use for
您可以使用的抽象
abstracting all those entities or of
抽象所有这些实体或
caching all those things you can also
缓存所有这些内容，您也可以
add in a second level cache e there you
在第二级缓存中添加您
can choose between maven and Gradle here
可以在这里选择Maven和Gradle
and how many of you may have in France
你们当中有多少人在法国
here still ok ok great so you can also
这里还是可以，很好，所以你也可以
choose between other technologies here
在这里选择其他技术
something like elastic search and things
诸如弹性搜索之类的东西
like that so if you have used - -
这样，如果您使用过--
blueprint buges here the only thing that
蓝图在这里臭虫唯一的
would be changed just like you will have
将会改变，就像你将有
an option called UJS that's one thing
一个叫做UJS的选项是一回事
that will be added and it will generate
将被添加，它将生成
an entire friend application for you so
一个完整的朋友应用程序为您
basically you can okay
基本上你可以
what
什么
yes here it is and it is a gradual
是的，这是一个渐进的过程
application so it's like I just have to
应用程序，就像我只需要
run craddle w
运行支架w
I think something some problem with my
我觉得我的东西有些问题
node modules but I'm not too sure about
节点模块，但我不太确定
it that's the reason why it is not
这就是为什么它不是这样的原因
working as expected okay so what it does
可以正常工作，所以它能做什么
is like it generates a bunch of
就像它产生了一堆
generator than application it has a
发电机比它具有的应用程序
plain spring boot based application and
基于纯Spring Boot的应用程序和
can showcase show the application so I
可以展示展示应用程序，所以我
can this is application that is
这是可以的应用程序吗
generated a plain Java based application
生成了一个基于Java的普通应用程序
with all the docker images that you
与您所有的码头工人图像
might need to run the application that
可能需要运行
also the Java part which is complete
也是完整的Java部分
spring boot based application there is
基于Spring Boot的应用程序
nothing fancy inside there and you have
里面没什么花哨的，你有
this web app which is completely made up
此网络应用程序完全组成
of you and typescript so we have written
你和打字稿，所以我们写了
the entire application ended application
整个应用结束的应用
and typescript and it also has view
和打字稿，它也有视图
components sprinkled over it
组件洒在上面
and it uses all the principles that you
它使用了您的所有原则
might want in a view comb view based
可能希望在基于视图的梳理视图中
application that's clearly segregated
明显分开的应用程序
like you have an admin module which has
就像你有一个管理模块
all those pages everything is segregated
所有这些页面一切都隔离了
into two own modules and all those best
分成两个自己的模块
practices that you need to follow when
您需要遵循的做法
you're trying to generate of UJS and if
您正在尝试生成UJS，如果
you want to learn UJS you can go to
你想学习UJS，你可以去
their website first and if you still
首先访问他们的网站，如果您仍然
want to have a practical information of
想要获得有关
how to align your application how to
如何调整您的应用程序
layout your application you can check
布置您可以检查的应用程序
this out because it is completely
这是因为它完全是
following the best practices that is
遵循最佳做法
listed by the community so here my
由社区列出，所以这里我
application is started so let me go
应用程序启动了，让我走
ahead here so here so this is the
在这里，所以这是
application that is generated and it
生成的应用程序及其
runs in view so it runs in view you have
在视图中运行，因此它在视图中运行
all those pages that you might that you
所有那些您可能会想要的页面
will have in Jeffster basic application
将在Jeffster中具有基本应用程序
generator you have a user management
生成器，您具有用户管理
module you have the metrics which list
模块中您具有列出的指标
of all the metrics of the JVM cache
JVM缓存的所有指标
statistics and HTTP requests and all
统计信息和HTTP请求以及所有
those things
那些事
it even has logging pages so the basic
它甚至具有日志记录页面，因此基本
difference here is like the page loading
这里的区别就像页面加载
is much more faster than compared with
比它快得多
the the modules or gesture modules a
模块或手势模块
pure friend and that we are generating
纯粹的朋友，我们正在产生
with angularjs as well as react so that
与angularjs以及反应，以便
is one of the major advantages that we
是我们的主要优势之一
have the entire chunk that we are
拥有了我们的全部
sending our resources that we are
发送我们的资源
sending to the front end this instill in
向前端发送此灌输
kilobytes it's not in megabytes that's
它不是以兆字节为单位
also one of the biggest advantage that
也是最大的优势之一
we have when we are trying to
当我们试图
when we move to UJS as you can see this
当我们移至UJS时，您可以看到
application has 1372 loggers which is
应用程序有1372个记录器
like a huge set of Dom tree that will be
就像一堆巨大的Dom树
generated for you but the page actually
为您生成，但页面实际
loaded pretty quickly then compared with
加载很快然后与
any other stuffs you have this API which
您拥有此API的其他任何东西
again uses Fagor api components so you
再次使用Fagor api组件，因此您
can see what your resources and things
可以看到你的资源和东西
like that does so this is basically what
这样就可以了，这基本上就是
will be generated by a gesture and VJs
将由手势和VJ生成
and we just released our version 1.0 and
我们刚刚发布了1.0版，
probably we are looking forward to move
也许我们期待着前进
forward to we are looking to move
向前，我们期待着前进
forward to make it even more better and
希望使它变得更好，并且
also any questions so far
到目前为止还有任何问题
nope okay view is actually small so when
不，好的视图实际上很小，所以当
I say small when you when you take
当你拿的时候我说小
angular into picture it actually goes up
变成图片，它实际上上升了
to two point three four megabytes for
到两点三四兆字节
the entire production-ready application
整个生产就绪的应用程序
that we are generating it has a lot of
我们正在生成它有很多
components inside it has at least 15 to
里面的组件至少有15个
20 pages inside so it takes around 2.3
里面有20页，大约需要2.3页
for with all the polyfills without
与所有的polyfills没有
polyfills it's around 1.3 3 megabytes on
polyfills大约是1.3 3兆字节
the other hand react takes almost 1
另一方面反应几乎需要1
megabyte so it's not gzip data we
兆字节，所以它不是gzip数据
haven't gzipped it but this is what
还没有将其压缩，但这就是
we're generating and the generated
我们正在生成
production output of the pack and
包装的生产产量和
finally boo JS it has just 571 kilobytes
终于嘘JS它只有571 KB
that's more than 50% of reduction then
那就是减少超过50％
compared with angular so that's one of
与角度相比，这是其中之一
the important things for the front end
前端重要的事情
applications the size here matters a lot
应用程序的大小在这里很重要
the amount of things that you're sending
您发送的东西数量
to your friend and as a resource makes
给你的朋友，作为一种资源
your application faster or slower that's
您的应用程序更快或更慢
very important to understand if you're
了解您是否很重要
developing a web based application the
开发基于Web的应用程序
size matters actually so what you can do
尺寸实际上很重要，所以您可以做什么
is here is like you can split those
在这里就像你可以拆分那些
entire chunks into multiple chunks to
整个块变成多个块
make sure that you're sending correct
确保您发送的是正确的
amount of data but again that from two
数据量，但又是两个
point three four megabytes to 571
将三四兆字节指向571
kilobytes it's like huge improvement for
千字节，对于
your application because the entire
您的应用程序，因为整个
library of view is pretty small in
图书馆的视野很小
angular for two point three four it
角两点三四
takes more than 60% of the space has
占用了超过60％的空间
been taken by the library itself and
由图书馆本身采取
remaining 40 percent is a code that we
剩下的40％是我们
actually generate on the other hand in a
另一方面实际产生
view the library is so small that you
查看图书馆是如此之小，以至于你
can gzip end it to 20 kilo bytes but
可以gzip将其结尾为20千字节，但是
it's just 20 kilo bytes that's added to
只是增加了20千字节
your payload so view the building of
您的有效载荷，因此请查看
views also faster as a developer this is
作为开发人员，查看速度也更快
some interesting fact for me or some
对我或某些有趣的事实
interesting metric that I am going to
我将要使用的有趣指标
use that helps me to understand how view
使用它可以帮助我了解视图
is actually built into it's really fast
实际上是内置的，速度非常快
in building view for example writing
在建筑物视图中，例如写作
angular for a production build it takes
生产所需的角度
almost 29 seconds for to complete
将近29秒才能完成
imagine you're running it in your
想象你在自己的机器上运行它
browser's or in your CI bills for a
浏览器或您的CI帐单中
production bill every bill takes 29
生产账单每张需要29
seconds to complete it and in react it's
秒完成它并做出反应
24 seconds this vise against improvement
虎钳24秒反对改进
is not a small thing it's a really big
这不是一件小事，而是一个很大的事情
thing because when you're running
事情是因为当你跑步时
thousands of times then it multiplies
成千上万倍
into that factor on the other hand and
另一方面，
view it takes just 22 seconds again yes
查看仅需22秒即可
you might be surprised it's like it's
您可能会感到惊讶，就像
not in tens or fifteen but it's not the
不是几十或十五，但这不是
case having seven seconds more or more
超过七秒的情况
to do the bill is huge number of time
办账单的时间很多
that you have it so that's why view is
你有它，所以这就是为什么视图是
actually helping in lot of things and
实际上在很多事情上都有帮助
also one other thing is like based on
另一件事是基于
the personal preference or based on
个人喜好或基于
running the applications and multiple
运行应用程序和多个
frameworks since I've worked on all this
自从我从事所有这些工作以来的框架
three frameworks it's pretty easy for
三个框架非常容易
you to understand the view code for a
您了解一个的视图代码
back-end developer it's very easy for
后端开发人员，对于
him to understand the view code then
然后他了解视图代码
compared with something that was written
与写的东西相比
on react with redux or sprinkled over it
与Redux反应或洒在其上
and angular on the other hand I just
另一方面，我只是
could help makes it a little bit easier
可以使它变得容易一些
for us to understand but again vue.js
让我们理解，但再次vue.js
has its own advantage then compared to
与之相比具有自己的优势
any other thing okay thanks for your
还有其他事情吗，谢谢您
time thank you
时间谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]
you
您